{
    "id": "52851325aed64fb6b1790de3031cfca8",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… need help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "Me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afc615f2f745467b880300a963863b29"
        },
        {
            "question": "It’s …………………………. that needs help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "you",
                "they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "284b10476a9d43a28fcd37b1545f0e9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "John has broken his leg. ........................................ will be in hospital for a few days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "He",
                "Him",
                "His"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf0060109feb48b3abb4620d2dfbb657"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tell Jane I miss .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ddb8c9596544455e99638053f64993d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane and Alice are friends. ......................................... like each other very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "Them",
                "She"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a8226358d40141a888e7f42183357a25"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Who’s that over there?’ ‘.................................. is Peter Cook.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "She",
                "It"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "65492b500bbe4a588e4d0435a2ac0218"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Hello. .................................. is Alan Williams.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "It",
                "He"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83b1d6aa0ed443d4b05e820de149d4aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mary is learning music. .......................................... has a golden voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "Her"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e54b2b66f8244f0590b52c4be0173e97"
        },
        {
            "question": "On Mary’s birthday, Alice gave ...................................... a watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac30e8e1634d4e3db872c87d9b81d5aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Harry is a brilliant student. ...................................... has won many prizes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "He",
                "Him",
                "They"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf1a448c91a1499abd464d2572ebadb2"
        }
    ]
}